Finding Aid for the Michael Braver Collection of Americanist Material LSC.1585
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Reel to Reel Tapes
  - Welch, Robert. (John Birch Society). If I Were President. Los Angeles, CA., March 1, 1968; (2 copies). (Box 3, 9, Box 24)
    - If I Were President, 1968 March 1; yrlsc_1585_002_003a; Welch, Robert, 1899-1985; John Birch Society; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:43:32) 7 inches (Box 3, Case 1)
      Transcribed from container: The Annual Council Dinner of the John Birch Society held on March 1, 1968 in the Century Plaza Hotel in Los Angeles, CA. Mr. Robert Welch delivered a major address: "If I Were President".
    - If I Were President, 1968 March 1; yrlsc_1585_002_003b; Welch, Robert, 1899-1985; John Birch Society; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:35:37) 7 inches (Box 3, Case 1)
  - Welch. Medicine Leads the Way. (pre-recorded), undated. (Box 23)
  - Welch. More Stately Mansions. Chicago., June 5, 1964. (Box 23)
  - Welch. More Truth about Vietnam. Pre-recorded., 1967. (Box 23)
  - Welch. Neutralism. Fullerton, CA., September 20, 1963. (Box 3, Box 23)
  - Welch. Our First Big Birthday Party. (JBS). New York., December 9, 1966. (Box 9, Box 25)
  - Welch. Robert Welch Testimonial. Hollywood, CA., October 11, 1965.; (2 copies). (Box 7, 9)
  - Welch. Success is in the Silences. Listed Under JBS Council Dinner., 1972. (Box 7, 9)
  - Welch. A Touch of Sanity. Thousand Oaks, CA., March 12, 1965. (Box 7, Box 24)
  - Welch. What is Communism. Santa Monica, CA., November 13, 1969. (Box 10, Box 24)
  - Welch. What is Communism. Pasadena, CA., November 10, 1969. (Box 23)
  - Welch. What is Communism. San Mateo, CA., January 18, 1970. (Box 23)
  - Westerfield, Rex. (JBS). John Birch Society Leadership Seminar. Burbank, CA., November 23, 1968. (Box 5, Box 24)
  - Westerfield. The John Birch Society Looks at Civil Turmoil. Thousand Oaks, CA., March 22, 1968. (Box 4, Box 24)
  - Willoughby, General C.A. Decline of the West. Christian Crusade., 1961. (Box 23)
  - Winegarner, Charles W. (Citizens Congressional Committee; possibly associate of Gerald Smith's Cross and Flag). Washington D.C, Under Siege. Los Angeles, CA., August 22, 1967. (Box 7, Box 25)
  - Wolff, (Prof.) Charles E. A Christian Approach to business Economics. Buena Park, CA., November 9, 1972. (Box 24)
  - Wolff, (Prof.) Charles E. What You and I Can Do to Help Stop the International Conspiracy. Long Beach, CA., May 22, 1971. (Box 3)
  - Wright, Ron. Regional Government. Long Beach, CA., April 10, 1973. (Box 23)
  - Wright, Ron. Untitled. at U.S.A. (United in Service to America). Encino, CA., January 1972. (Box 23)
  - Wurmbrand, (Pastor) Richard. Tortured for Christ. Los Angeles., February 13, 1968. (Box 2, Box 23)
  - Wurmbrand. Tortured for Christ. Oxnard, CA., January 18, 1973. (Box 25)